Explore the meaning of falling stars, meteorites and deep impacts.
Fireball: Visitors from Darker Worlds is a
documentary film directed by Werner Herzog.
This remarkable journey across our planet and universe explores how meteorites, shooting stars, and
deep impacts have awoken our wonder about other realms—and make us rethink our destinies.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Werner Herzog.
Self, played by Clive Oppenheimer.
Self, played by Simon Schaffer.
Self, played by Jon Larsen.
Fireball: Visitors from Darker Worlds is a 2020 documentary film
directed by Werner Herzog and Clive Oppenheimer.
The film explores the cultural, spiritual, and scientific impact of
meteorites, and the craters they create around the globe.
It had its world premiere at the Toronto International
Film Festival on September 10, 2020.
It was released on Apple TV+ on November 13, 2020.
The film explores themes of meteor, space, science.
The tone is thought_provoking.